OSMANY PUJOL

GitHub: https://github.com/SDOsmany

Miami, FL 33183

Osmany.pujolcs@gmail.com

7863667932

I have 2 years of experience working with web design and development using Tools
like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, MySQL, Python, Rest APIs, Postman, Git, GitHub, Trello board and Jira and lots of
experience working alongside other developers. Check out the most recent project I worked on at:

https://github.com/CodeforSouth/peoplebudget-beta
and PeopleBudget.org

Authorized to work in the US for any employer



WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer

Code for South - Miami, FL December 2019 to September 2020

I worked with Code for south in the development on a web application called People

Budget for the City of Miami. We created a product for the City of Miami to be able to gather data with regards to how the budget for the city should be spent and working to educate the community about participatory budget

Freelance Web Developer

Upwork - Miami, FL April 2019 to August 2020

I have delivered many products to clients at Upwork in the web development field



EDUCATION

Associate in Computer Science

Miami Dade College - Miami, FL August 2018 to Present



----- SKILLS

- CSS
- HTML5
- Node.js
- React
- JavaScript
- Git
- Bootstrap
- Web Development
- Python
- MySQL
- REST
- JSON
- GitHub
- APIs
- User Interface (UI)
- PHP
- Unit Testing
- Java
- English



LINKS

https://github.com/CodeforSouth/peoplebudget-beta

https://github.com/SDOsmany?tab=repositories